[
   {
     "question": "Beruf",
     "answer": "Profession",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "packungen",
     "answer": "packs",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Freundschaft",
     "answer": "Friendship",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Reisen",
     "answer": "Travel",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Universität",
     "answer": "university",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Erfahrung",
     "answer": "Experience",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Schwierig",
     "answer": "Difficult",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Glücklich",
     "answer": "Happy",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Interessant",
     "answer": "Interesting",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Verantwortung",
     "answer": "Responsibility",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Beziehung",
     "answer": "Relationship",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Gesellschaft",
     "answer": "Company",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Kultur",
     "answer": "Culture",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Sprache",
     "answer": "Language",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Fortschritt",
     "answer": "Progress",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Herausforderung",
     "answer": "Challenge",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Entscheidung",
     "answer": "Decision",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Verständnis",
     "answer": "Understanding",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Entwicklung",
     "answer": "Development",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Möglichkeiten",
     "answer": "Possibilities",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Kommunikation",
     "answer": "communication",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Leidenschaft",
     "answer": "Passion",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Gesundheit",
     "answer": "Health",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Umwelt",
     "answer": "Environment",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Technologie",
     "answer": "technology",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Erinnerung",
     "answer": "Memory",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Gelegenheit",
     "answer": "Opportunity",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Erfolg",
     "answer": "Success",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Veränderung",
     "answer": "change",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Wissenschaft",
     "answer": "Science",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Fähigkeit",
     "answer": "Capability",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Wirtschaft",
     "answer": "Business",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Natürlich",
     "answer": "Naturally",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Zufriedenheit",
     "answer": "satisfaction",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Vertrauen",
     "answer": "Trust",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Aufregend",
     "answer": "Exciting",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Leistung",
     "answer": "Performance",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Entdecken",
     "answer": "Discover",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Verstehen",
     "answer": "Understand",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Erneuerbar",
     "answer": "Renewable",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Zusammenarbeit",
     "answer": "Cooperation",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Verantwortungsbewusst",
     "answer": "Responsible",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Unterstützung",
     "answer": "Support",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Vielfalt",
     "answer": "diversity",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Herausragend",
     "answer": "Outstanding",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Ausdruck",
     "answer": "Expression",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Zusammenhang",
     "answer": "Connection",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Entschlossenheit",
     "answer": "determination",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Energie",
     "answer": "energy",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Gemeinschaft",
     "answer": "Community",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Überzeugung",
     "answer": "conviction",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Leidenschaftlich",
     "answer": "Passionate",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Herausfordernd",
     "answer": "Challenging",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Ermutigung",
     "answer": "encouragement",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Nachhaltigkeit",
     "answer": "sustainability",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Verständigung",
     "answer": "understanding",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Bemerkenswert",
     "answer": "Remarkable",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Erkunden",
     "answer": "Explore",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Einfluss",
     "answer": "Influence",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Empathie",
     "answer": "empathy",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Gerechtigkeit",
     "answer": "justice",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Kooperation",
     "answer": "cooperation",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Entschlossen",
     "answer": "Determined",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Beharrlichkeit",
     "answer": "persistence",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Kreativität",
     "answer": "creativity",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Initiative",
     "answer": "initiative",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Anpassungsfähig",
     "answer": "Adaptable",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Innovativ",
     "answer": "Innovative",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Aufmerksamkeit",
     "answer": "Attention",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Rücksichtnahme",
     "answer": "thoughtfulness",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Lebendig",
     "answer": "Lively",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Aufgeschlossen",
     "answer": "Open minded",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Visionär",
     "answer": "Visionary",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Neugierig",
     "answer": "Curious",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Großzügig",
     "answer": "Generous",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Achtsamkeit",
     "answer": "Mindfulness",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Zusammenhalt",
     "answer": "cohesion",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Gleichberechtigung",
     "answer": "equal rights",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Verantwortungsvoll",
     "answer": "Responsible",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Ehrgeizig",
     "answer": "Ambitious",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "Respektvoll",
     "answer": "Respectful",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "beim Weiterlernen",
     "answer": "When learning",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "vorstellung",
     "answer": "performance",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "beratung",
     "answer": "advice",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "sprechtag",
     "answer": "speaking day",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "schach",
     "answer": "chess",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "gemeinsames",
     "answer": "common",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "sprachtreff",
     "answer": "speech meeting",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "netzpolitik",
     "answer": "network policy",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "politik",
     "answer": "politics",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "sprecherin",
     "answer": "spokeswoman",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "bereitung",
     "answer": "preparation",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "die zeitung",
     "answer": "the newspaper",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "komödie",
     "answer": "comedy",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "lieb",
     "answer": "dear",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "backen",
     "answer": "bake",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "kekse",
     "answer": "cookies",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "sei",
     "answer": "may be",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "nichte",
     "answer": "niece",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "ferien",
     "answer": "holidays",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "feieren",
     "answer": "celebrate",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "das gepäck",
     "answer": "the luggage",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "der abflug",
     "answer": "the takeoff",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "abfahrt",
     "answer": "Departure",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "blumenladen",
     "answer": "flower shop",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "bioladen",
     "answer": "organic shop",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "jemand",
     "answer": "someone",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "bald",
     "answer": "soon",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "holt",
     "answer": "get",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "wiederkommen",
     "answer": "come back",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "ausschlafen",
     "answer": "sleep in",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "strand",
     "answer": "beach",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "wem",
     "answer": "whom",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "denn",
     "answer": "then",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "dann",
     "answer": "then",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "wenn",
     "answer": "if",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "wann",
     "answer": "When",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "unordentlich",
     "answer": "messy",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "verärgert",
     "answer": "annoyed",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "miete",
     "answer": "rent",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "kassenzettel",
     "answer": "Bill",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "genug",
     "answer": "enough",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "gebrochen",
     "answer": "Broken",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "hilfreich",
     "answer": "helpful",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "ehefrau",
     "answer": "wife",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "ehemann",
     "answer": "husband",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "unhöflich",
     "answer": "impolite",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "leer",
     "answer": "empty",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "leiser",
     "answer": "quieter",
     "score": 0
   },
   {
     "question": "pflanzen",
     "answer": "plan",
     "score": 0
   }
 ]